YOUNG JUDY:
Fear. Treachery. Bloodlust.
Thousands of years ago...
these were the forces
that ruled our world.
A world where prey
were scared of predators.
And predators had an uncontrollable...
biological urge...
to maim, and maul, and...
(GASPS)
- (ROARS)
- (SCREAMS)
- Blood! Blood! Blood!
- (AUDIENCE GASPING)
(CHOKING)
(GROANING)
And death.
(GROANS)
(AUDIENCE MURMURING)
(DRAMATIC DRUMMING)
Back then, the world was divided in two.
- Vicious predator...
- (GROWLS)
or meek prey.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
JUDY:
But over time, we evolved.
And moved beyond
our primitive, savage ways.
Now, predator and prey live in harmony.
(SQUEAKS)
And every young mammal has
multitudinous opportunities.
Yeah.
I don't have to cower in a herd anymore.
Instead, I can be an astronaut.
- (PLAYING EERIE MUSIC)
- (AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
I don't have to be
a lonely hunter anymore.
Today, I can hunt for tax exemptions.
I'm gonna be an actuary!
(PLAYING PATRIOTIC MUSIC)
And I can make the world a better place.
I am going to be...
(FUNKY MUSIC PLAYING)
A police officer!
(YOUNG GIDEON LAUGHING)
Bunny cop?
That is the most
stupidest thing I ever heard.
It may seem impossible
to small minds...
I'm looking at you, Gideon Grey.
(AUDIENCE CHUCKLING)
But, just 211 miles away...
stands the great city of Zootopia!
Where our ancestors first
joined together in peace...
and declared that anyone
can be anything!
- (ORGAN MUSIC PLAYING)
- (AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
Thank you and good night!
STU: Judy, you ever wonder
how your mom and me...
got to be so darn happy?
Nope.
Well, we gave up on our dreams
and we settled. Right, Bon?
Oh, yes, that's right, Stu.
We settled hard.
See, that's the beauty
of complacency, Jude.
If you don't try anything new,
you'll never fail.
I like trying actually.
What you father means, hon...
is it's gonna be difficult...
impossible even, for you
to become a police officer.
Right. There's never been a bunny cop.
- No.
- Bunnies don't do that.
- Never.
Oh. Then, I guess
I'll have to be the first one.
Because I am gonna make...
- the world a better place.
- (STU CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Or, uh, heck,
you know, you want to talk...
about making the world
a better place...
no better way to do it than
becoming a carrot farmer.
Yes! Your dad, me...
your 275 brothers and sisters.
- We're changing the world!
- Yeah.
- One carrot at a time.
- Amen to that.
Carrot farming is a noble profession.
- Mmm-hmm.
- (CHILDREN LAUGHING)
BONNIE: Just putting the seeds
in the ground.
STU: Ah, at one with the soil.
Just getting covered in dirt.
- (SIGHS)
- BONNIE: You get it, honey.
It's great to have dreams.
Yeah. Just as long as you don't...
believe in them too much.
Where'd the heck she go?
YOUNG GIDEON:
Give me your tickets right now...
or I'm gonna kick your...
- meek little sheep butt.
- Ow!
Cut it out, Gideon!
Baa! Baa!
What are you gonna do? Cry?
Hey! You heard her. Cut it out.
Nice costume, loser.
What crazy world are you living in...
where you think
a bunny could be a cop?
Kindly return my friend's tickets.
Come and get them.
But watch out, because I'm a fox...
and like you said in your
dumb little stage play...
us predators used to eat prey.
And that killer instinct
is still in our "Dunnah."
Uh, I'm pretty much sure
it's pronounced "DNA."
Don't tell me what I know, Travis.
You don't scare me, Gideon.
- (GROANS)
- YOUNG GIDEON: You scared now?
TRAVIS:
Look at her nose twitch!
She is scared!
Cry little baby bunny.
Cry, Cry...
- (YOUNG JUDY GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
(ALL GASPS)
Oh, you don't know
when to quit, do you?
- (GASPS)
- (GROWLS)
(YOUNG JUDY SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
I want you to remember this moment...
the next time you think...
you will ever be anything more
than just a stupid...
- carrot-farming, dumb bunny.
- (WHIMPERS)
(LAUGHS)
(ALL PANTING)
That looks bad.
Are you okay, Judy?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm okay.
- Here you go.
- Oh!
Wow! You got our tickets!
You're awesome, Judy!
Yeah, that Gideon Grey doesn't
know what he's talking about.
Well, he was right about one thing.
I don't know when to quit.
DRILL INSTRUCTOR:
Listen up, cadets.
Zootopia has 12 unique...
ecosystems within its city limits.
Tundratown...
Sahara Square...
Rainforest District, to name a few.
You're gonna have
to master all of them...